## MAKSYM MEDVEDIEV

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

## Personal info

Date of birth: 27/09/1997
Nationality: Ukrainian
Address: Odessa, Ukraine

Phone number: +380501643943

**Email address:** medmmax@gmail.com **Web:** https://github.com/A1doranM **Skype:** live:f5d8752ce8d90d5c

**Telegram:** Medevac137 **Work type:** Remote, Office

## **Profile**

I want to continue my career in information technology, growing as a specialist in my field. In addition to improving Frontend Development skills. I also continue to improve my skills in backend, database, software architecture, mathematics and algorithms.

## Work experience

05/2023 - now

## **Software Developer**

## **Phobosys / Dreamhost**

As Full-Stack developer I was working on dreamhost website (https://www.dreamhost.com/) and website management system usign React, Redux, Saga, PropTypes i18next on front-end and NodeJS, Typescript, AWS-SDK, inversify, express on back-end.

## Work experience

04/2024 - 11/2024

## **Senior Software Developer**

## **Hearty App**

Working as Full-Stack (Node, React, NextJS) and Mobile (Flutter/Dart) developer on Hearty Application for kids and their parents.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=vision.pathfinder.iparent&pcampaignid=web\_share

https://apps.apple.com/ua/app/hearty-app-everyday-bonding/id1567076603?I=ru

09/2022 - 03/2023

## **Senior Software Developer**

#### Moohii

As React, and Next.js developer I was working on couple of Ukraine government projects from September 2022 to March 2023 which will be the part of the Dia ecosystem.

- First it is online eco-certificate for Ukraine Ministery of Ecology for extraction and delivery of timber.
- Second it is drova-e website as part of Dia ecosystem where timber companies can sell firewood, and the population can buy it. (https://drovae.gov.ua/)

04/2022 - 08/2022

## Software engineer PlayTech

I worked on the front-end part of CMS system and portal for this system using React, Redux and WebSockets.

## Work experience

01/2021 - 04/2022

## Software engineer

#### Exadel

As a developer, I worked on the part of several sites, one of them was inner company project about workers assessment based on React and Express with MySQL, another one was ABC Fitness Solutions project for managing fitness clubs. (React and Java with JSP + MySQL)

10/2019 - 11/2020

## Full-stack web developer, Android (Java) developer, Android (Dart/Flutter) developer DigitalMaker

Developed advertising platform using React and NestJS and PostgreSQL.

Created Flutter and native Android mobile Apps with NestJS on backend and Firebase

01/2018 - 02/2019

## Java and Androidl internship Luxoft

Development and presentation of the Android application with development organization process according to Agile methodology. The project was to create an application for snowboarders and those who want to become one of them.

01/2018 - 02/2019

# PythonDeveloper Joint project of ONPU and Augsburg university. "Neurobotics" Odessa

Aims of our project was to train self-driving car with OpenCV wand neural network. I learned OpenCV framework, and prepared data for training neural network.

## **Skills**

#### LANGUAGES:

English - **B2** Ukrainian - **Native** Deutsch - **B1** Russian - **Native** 

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPING:**

JavaScriptReact/ReduxSQLNestSASSNodeJSPostgreSQLNext.jsPrisma ORMGitRESTRollup

Graph QL JWT Webpack Storybook

Redis Bootstrap RDF/RQDFS JEST, Enzyme

Python FastAPI SQL Alchemy

#### **DEPLOYMENT:**

AWS Docker Kubernetes

#### **PROCESSES:**

Agile SCRUM

### **METHODOLOGIES AND PRINCIPLES:**

BEM SOLID GRASP GOF

## **Education**

09/2015 - 11/2020 Software engineering | Master of Science
Odessa National Polytechnic University